(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.0b1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 5,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 1000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
こんわー！こよりだよー！
Konwa! It's Koyori!
せーの！こっこよりー！
One, two! Kokkoyori!
はい！ハッシュタグ #こより日記 チャレンジ
Yes! Hashtag #KoyoriNikki Challenge!
オーケー！ぽよ！
Okay! Poyo!
ずーめす ずーめす ずーめす
Zoomesu zoomesu zoomesu!
ボディチェック？
Body check?
はい！やったー！
Yes! I did it!
こよりスケッチ
Koyori Sketch!
てれーん！はい！
Ta-da! Yes!
めー！せーの！
Meh! One, two!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
勉強さらじ自慢
Study session bragging!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ひまわり知天間
Himawari Chitenka!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こよりの朝食ワンミール
Koyori's breakfast one-meal!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こんわー！ヘルプ！
Konwa! Help!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！どんびよー！
Uwah! Donbiyo!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
嘘まなんてね！にあたう！
Just kidding! Niatta!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
かわいいですでや！
It's cute, deya!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
オーケー！こっこよりー！
Okay! Kokkoyori!
さあ！
Now!
よっしゃー！
All right!
間に合ったー！
I made it!
マヨネーズは飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
なににむすだちは好きです
I love Sudachi with everything!
はい！お肉！全巻！
Yes! Meat! All volumes!
冷凍うどんは常備してます
I always have frozen udon ready!
どうですか？はい！やったー！
How's that? Yes! I did it!
証明完了！Q.E.D.！
Proof complete! Q.E.D.!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こくだろこっくん！
Kokudaro kokkun!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うりまりはちょびんすくる
Urimari is chobinschool!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
五食間？ういういういうい！
Five meals a day? Yes-yes-yes-yes!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！いきませんね！
Uwah! No good!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
おもしまーす！しょなー！
Enjoying! Shona!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
午後のプログラムは復活！
The afternoon program is back!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あー！あいもこより！
Ah! Aimokoyori!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うー！
Ooh!
よっしゃー！
All right!
間に合ったー！
I made it!
マヨネーズは飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
なににむすだちは好きです
I love Sudachi with everything!
はい！お肉！全巻！
Yes! Meat! All volumes!
冷凍うどんは常備してます
I always have frozen udon ready!
どうですか？はい！やったー！
How's that? Yes! I did it!
私の戦闘力は54万です！
My power level is 540,000!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うさぎさんは17歳です！
The rabbit is 17 years old!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こよのおいすし商店だよ！
It's Koyo's Oisushi Shop!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
てけのかで！そこが好き！
Tekenoka! I love that part!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うわー！150-50！
Uwah! 150-50!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
シャツは飲み物ではありません！
Shirts are not a drink!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こつこつ唐揚げでや！
Crunchy fried chicken, deya!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
しっぽもふきふき！だめです！
Tail-rubbing! No way!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
みんなの応援がひとまろだよ！
Everyone's support is my strength!
右手ー！
Right hand!
よっしゃー！
All right!
間に合ったー！
I made it!
マヨネーズは飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink!
なににむすだちは好きです
I love Sudachi with everything!
はい！お肉！全巻！
Yes! Meat! All volumes!
冷凍うどんは常備してます
I always have frozen udon ready!
どうですか？はい！やったー！
How's that? Yes! I did it!
せーの！
One, two!
こっこよりー！
Kokkoyori!
こよりは マヨネーズ で 回復 した
[Visual Text: Koyori recovered with mayonnaise]
助手くんが仲間になった！
[Visual Text: Joshu-kun joined the party!]
AIこよりが仲間になった！
[Visual Text: AI Koyori joined the party!]
もふこよが仲間になった！
[Visual Text: Mofukoyo joined the party!]
へい！カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Hey! Like the morning sun illuminating Kalos,
（ニトロチャージ熱く行こうぜ）
(Nitro Charge, let's go hot!)
さあ！進もうぜ いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's proceed, we're always ready, OK.
（かたやぶりへんげんじざいで）
(Breaking through, ever-changing!)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
Our overlapping feelings sync up,
決して消えない絆になるから
and become a bond that will never disappear.
どこまでも強くなれる
We can become stronger no matter how far,
俺たちなら woh woh woh yeah
if it's us, woh woh woh yeah!
いくZ！！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go Z!! A fiercely burning battle,
いくZ！！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
let's go Z!! A crisis is an opportunity!
いこうZ！！きしかいせい 絶対に諦めない
Let's go Z!! Desperate struggle, we'll never give up!
俺たちは諦めない
We will never give up!
へい！例えどんな壁が道を塞いだって
Hey! Even if any kind of wall blocks the road,
（いつでも当たって砕けろで）
(always hit it and break through!)
さあ！こうぜ いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's go, we're always ready, OK.
（かたやぶりへんげんじざいで）
(Breaking through, ever-changing!)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
Our overlapping feelings sync up,
決して消えない絆になるから
and become a bond that will never disappear.
どこまでも強くなれる
We can become stronger no matter how far,
俺たちなら woh woh woh yeah
if it's us, woh woh woh yeah!
いくZ！！手強いライバルたち
Let's go Z!! Formidable rivals,
いくZ！！決めろ一撃必殺
let's go Z!! Land a one-hit knockout!
いこうZ！！負けられない 想いがここにあるから
Let's go Z!! We can't lose, our feelings are right here.
夢が俺にはあるから
Because I have a dream!
博衣こよ理生誕ライブ2026、見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Hakuui Koyori Birthday Live 2026!
神ゲーたちの神ゲームソングをいっぱい詰め込んでるのだ！
I've packed in lots of god-tier game songs from god-tier games!
最後まで楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy until the very end!
いくZ！！勝ちも負けも 痛みも
Let's go Z!! Victory, defeat, and the pain too,
いくZ！！何でも分かち合える
let's go Z!! we can share everything.
いこうZ！！仲間がいる 俺たちは独りじゃない
Let's go Z!! I have comrades, we are not alone!
いくZ！！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go Z!! A fiercely burning battle,
いくZ！！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
let's go Z!! A crisis is an opportunity!
いこうZ！！きしかいせい 絶対に諦めない
Let's go Z!! Desperate struggle, we'll never give up!
いくZ！！譲れない夢がある
Let's go Z!! There's a dream I can't yield,
いくZ！！必ずゲットだぜ
let's go Z!! we'll definitely get it!
いこうZ！！手を伸ばして いつか描いた未来へ
Let's go Z!! Reach out to the future we once envisioned,
誰も知らない高みへ
to the heights that no one knows.
さあ！上げてくぜ（100万ボルト）
Come on! Let's crank it up (1 Million Volts)!
そう！立ち向かって 共にいこうぜ
Yes! Let's face it and go together,
見たことのない 夢の向こうまで
to the other side of a dream never seen before!
はーい！みんな！こんこよー！
Hi everyone! Konkoyo!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよ理だよー！
I'm the brain of Secret Society holoX, Hololive's 6th gen Hakuui Koyori!
改めて今日は、博衣こよ理生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you so much for coming to Hakuui Koyori Birthday Live 2026!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう！イェーイ！かっこいい？見えてるよ！ありがとう！
Thanks for all the comments too! Yay! Do I look cool? I see you! Thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショはハッシュタグを付けてたくさん呟いてね！
So, please tweet your thoughts and screenshots with the hashtag!
...ポストしてください！
...please post about it!
目指せトレンド入り、よろしくだああ！
Aim for the trending list, please!
はい、ということで、ちょっと息が整ってないですけど...
Yes, so, I'm a bit out of breath, but...
さて、今年の生誕ライブ、テーマは...
Now, this year's birthday live theme is...
『ゲームソングライブ』です！
"Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた実況配信で 一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや
From the many game streams I've done so far, games full of memories we've played together,
こよが大好きなゲーム関連の楽曲をたくさん詰め込みました！
and songs related to games Koyo loves, I've packed so many of them in!
最後まで全力で楽しんでってね！
Please enjoy yourselves to the fullest until the very end!
ということで、1曲目は大好きなポケモンのXYZを歌わせていただきました！ねー！
So, for the first song, I sang XYZ from my favorite, Pokemon! Right!
助手くーん！
Josh-kuuuun!
はい。俺はこいつと旅に出る、っていうことで。
Yes. "I'm going on a journey with this guy," just like that.
はい。Xでセトリ予想もね、みんなにたくさんしてもらってたんですけど、
Yes. I had everyone do lots of setlist predictions on X too,
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったけど、XYZ当てられてる人は結構少なかったです。
and while there were many Pokemon guesses, quite few people correctly predicted XYZ.
当たった君、おめでとう！
To those who got it right, congratulations!
ま、この曲は、ま、Z-Aが発売になったっていうのもあるんですけど、
Well, for this song, part of it is because Legends Z-A was announced,
歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもピッタリな曲なので選びました。
but the lyrics are so good and it's actually a perfect song for Koyo, so I chose it.
さあ、このあとも自分の予想が当たってるかなーって、ドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください。
Now, please continue to enjoy while feeling nervous about whether your predictions will come true.
新3Dお披露目もあるからね！絶対最後まで見てってね！
There's also a new 3D reveal! Make sure to watch until the very end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲。
Now, it's about time for the next song.
ゲームの世界へ、どうぞ！
Into the world of games, please!
[キャラクター選択]
[Visual: Character Select]
[ロード中...]
[Visual: Loading...]
エアーマンが倒せない
I Can't Beat Airman
作詞：せら / たかにそ 作曲：せら
Lyrics: Sera / Takaniso Composition: Sera
気がついたら 同じ面ばかりプレイ
When I realized it, I was playing the same level,
そしていつも 同じ場所で死ぬ
and always dying in the same place.
あきらめずに 消える足場に挑戦するけど
I don't give up, I keep challenging the disappearing platforms,
すぐに下が落ちるよー
but I fall straight down.
「アイテム2号」があれば 楽に向こうの岸まで着くけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other shore,
何回やっても 何回やっても
but no matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ！
I can't beat Airman!
あの竜巻何回やってもよけれない！
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those tornadoes!
後ろに回って打ち続けるけれど いずれ風に飛ばされる
I try to go behind and keep shooting, but eventually, I get blown away by the wind.
タイム連打を試してみたけど 竜巻相手じゃ意味が無い！！
I tried button-mashing the time, but it's meaningless against the tornado!!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, to win next time,
僕は「E缶」だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save only the E-Tank until the very end.
気がついたら 「ライフ」もう少しかない
When I realized, I had only a little bit of life left,
吸収つもそこで「E缶」使う
and I always use an E-Tank there.
あきらめずに エアーマンまでたどり着くけれど
I don't give up, I reach Airman,
すぐにザンキなくなる
but I run out of lives immediately.
リーフシールドがあれば 楽にエアーマンを倒せるけど
If I had Leaf Shield, I could easily beat Airman,
何回やっても 何回やっても
but no matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
ウッドマンがたおせないよ！！
I can't beat Woodman!!
落ちる木の葉は 何回やってもよけれない！
No matter how many times I try, I can't dodge those falling leaves!
後ろに下がって 距離をとっても いずれ距離をつめられる
Even if I go behind and keep my distance, eventually, the distance is closed.
タイム連打を試してみたけど あいつのジャンプはくぐれない！
I tried button-mashing the time, but I can't slip past his jump!
だけど次は絶対勝つために
So, to win next time,
僕は「E缶」だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save only the E-Tank until the very end.
「アイテム2号」があれば 楽に向こうの岸まで着くけど
If I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other shore,
何回やっても 何回やっても
but no matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ！
I can't beat Airman!
あの竜巻...
Those tornadoes...
あの竜巻何回やっても避けれない
I couldn't dodge the tornado,
no matter how many times I try.
うしろに回って撃ち続けても
Despite jumping behind and firing repeatedly,
いずれは風に飛ばされる
I get blown off eventually.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I even tried rapid time firing,
竜巻相手じゃ意味が無い
but it's meaningless against the tornado.
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, in order to win the next round,
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
I'll save the E tank until the very last moment!
倒せないよ
I can't defeat him...
ロボのテーマ
[BGM: Robo's Theme]
カエルのテーマ
[BGM: Frog's Theme]
Melodies Of Life
[Song: Melodies of Life]
あてもなくさまよっていた
I was wandering aimlessly,
手がかりもなく探し続けた
searching without a single clue.
あなたがくれた思い出を
The memories you gave to me...
心を癒す歌にして
I'll turn them into a song to heal my heart.
...歌にして
...into a song to heal my heart.
約束もすることもなく
Without making promises,
交わす言葉も決めたりもせず
without deciding what words to say.
抱きしめ そして確かめた
You held me, and then I was certain:
日々は二度と帰らぬ
we could never go back to those days.
記憶の中の
You, waving your hand
手を振るあなたは
in my memories...
私の名を
Can you
呼ぶことができるの
call my name?
溢れるその涙を
Turn those overflowing tears
輝く勇気に変えて
into glittering courage.
命は続く
Life goes on,
夜を越え
across the night,
疑うことのない
and continues to
明日へと続く
a certain tomorrow.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
To the sky beyond the flying birds,
幾つの記憶預けただろう
how many memories were entrusted?
儚い希望も夢も
Short-lived hopes and dreams
届かぬ場所に忘れて
are forgotten in an unreachable place.
巡り合うのは偶然と言えるの
Can you say our meeting was coincidence,
別れる時が必ず来るのに
even though the time will surely come when we part?
消えゆく運命でも
Even though fate is fleeting,
君が生きている限り
as long as you live...
命は続く
Life goes on,
永遠に
eternally.
命は続く
Life goes on,
永遠に
eternally,
その力の限りどこまでも
to anywhere, as long as you're strong.
私が死のうとも
Though I may die,
君が生きている限り
as long as you live...
命は続く
Life goes on,
永遠に
eternally.
命は続く
Life goes on,
永遠に
eternally,
その力の限りどこまでも
to anywhere, as long as you're strong,
続く
continues.
きみの瞳に映る
What color am I
わたしは何色ですか
in your eyes?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう陽の光を
I will give you the sunlight.
キミガタメ
[Song: Kimi ga Tame]
悲しみが溢れ
Overflowing with sadness,
瞼閉じました
I closed my eyelids.
こぼれた滴は
The spilled drops
心に沁みゆく
sink into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The spreading waves
弱く交えます
mix weakly.
とどけしゆりかご
Reach for the cradle,
眠りをさそう
that invites sleep.
夢になつかし
In a nostalgic dream,
面影をさがす
I search for the silhouette.
手を伸ばし 強く
I stretch out my hand,
抱きしめたくなる
and I want to hold you tightly.
ha-
きみの瞳に映る
What color am I
わたしは何色ですか
in your eyes?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo,
渡そう高き空を
I will give you the high sky.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
repeating encounters and partings.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
traveler through time.
あなたが泣いている
You are crying,
流るる涙の雨
in the rain of flowing tears.
泣くなとは言わない
I won't say not to cry,
心かなしくて
for my heart is sad.
生きとし生けるもの
All living things,
何かを背負いながら
while carrying a burden,
見えない鎖につながれている
are connected by invisible chains.
どれほど救われただろう
How much I must have been saved,
あどけない笑顔を なくしたくはない
I don't want to lose that innocent smile.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す過去と未来
repeating past and future.
生まれそして死んでゆく運命
A fate of being born and then dying,
掛け違えた世界で
in a world where paths crossed wrong.
繰り返す出会いと別れ
Repeating encounters and partings.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時かける旅人
traveler through time.
戦闘開始!!
[Visual: Battle Start!!]
穢れのない心
While dyeing a pure heart
黒く染めゆきながら
into deep black,
抑えられなくて解き放たれる
it cannot be suppressed and is unleashed.
何回名を呼んだだろう
How many times have I called your name?
あどけない笑顔はもうどこにもない
That innocent smile is nowhere to be found.
不安定な神様
Unstable God...
引き継いだ夢と愛を
Inherited dreams and love
育て守り託しゆく 運命
Raising, protecting, and entrusting... Fate
掛け違えた世界で
In a world crossed incorrectly
探すため引き裂かれても
Even if torn apart to search
また会えると信じて
Believing that we can meet again
時かける旅人
A traveler chasing time
不安定な神様
Unstable God
繰り返す過去と未来
Repeating past and future
生まれそして死んでいく 運命
Born and dying... Fate
掛け違えた世界で
In a world crossed incorrectly
繰り返す出会いと別れ
Repeating meetings and partings
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again
時かける旅人
A traveler chasing time
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again
時かける旅人
A traveler chasing time
はい！ということで
Alright! And so,
Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
we had Suara-san come over and sing with me!
Suaraさん、自己紹介をいただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, would you mind introducing yourself?
はい、Suaraです。
Yes, I am Suara.
『うたわれるもの』シリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です。
I'm the one who sings many theme songs for the 'Utawarerumono' series.
はーい！ようこそー！
Yes! Welcome!
あ、こよりさん！あー！
Oh, Koyori-san! Ah!
そうなんです、実はですね、
That's right, actually...
『うたわれるもの』というゲーム、
Regarding the game 'Utawarerumono',
昨年約3ヶ月間かけて、シリーズ三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれども、
last year I spent about 3 months doing a Let's Play of the trilogy...
その『うたわれるもの』、本当に曲がめちゃくちゃいいのですが、
And 'Utawarerumono' has such incredibly good music,
その歌をほぼ全てSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃると…！
and Suara-san sings almost all of those songs...!
のです！はい！
She does! Yes!
もう耳が今日本当に幸せで！
My ears are just so happy today!
いや、こちらこそですよ、本当に！
No, the pleasure is all mine, really!
恐縮、恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、ありがとうございます！
I'm feeling quite humbled and overwhelmed, but thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Suaraさんには実は、4周年の時に逆凸でメッセージも頂戴しておりまして、
I actually received a message from Suara-san during my 4th anniversary call-in segment,
その時にいつか一緒に歌いたいというのも、こよりも結構熱烈なラブコールをさせていただいていたんですけれども、
and at that time, I sent a very passionate 'love call' saying I wanted to sing together someday.
その想いを本日叶えることができました！わー！
And today, I was able to make that dream come true! Yay!
え、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけれども、
Um, well, I have a few questions...
実は『うたわれるもの』の実況してた時に、
Actually, while I was streaming 'Utawarerumono',
最終回でSuaraさんがコメントしてくださっていまして、
Suara-san left a comment during the final episode,
こよりの実況ちょっとご覧くださったと思うんですけれども、
so I think you watched a bit of my stream...
見られますか？実況とかって普段。
Do you usually watch game streams?
いや、ちょっと実はですね、初めて見させていただいて。
Well, actually, that was the first time I've ever watched one.
そうなんですか！
Is that so!
そうなんです。あ、えっと、アクアプラスのね、スタッフの方とかからも、
Yes. Um, well, even from the staff at Aquaplus,
「こよりさんっていう『うたわれ』配信してるよ」って言って、
they told me, "There's someone named Koyori-san streaming 'Utaware',"
情報は聞いていたんですよね。
so I had heard the news.
で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも、
And also from the fans who come to my live concerts,
「ぜひ見てみてください」って言って。
they were saying, "You should definitely check it out."
それで、見させていただいたっていうのが、最終回だったんですけれども。
So, the first time I watched it was that final episode.
そうだったんですね！恐縮です！
I see! I'm so honored!
いえいえ、もう、すごい、本当に、こう、こよりさんの『うたわれるもの』への愛が、
Not at all. I mean, it was amazing, really. Your love for 'Utawarerumono'...
すごい溢れてて、本当に見てて、もう最後までずっと、
it was just overflowing. Watching it, all the way to the end,
うー！
Ooh!
見させていただいて。
I watched it.
で、「あ、コメント送りたいな」って。
And I thought, "Oh, I want to send a comment."
「あ、でももう早くしないと終わっちゃう！」と思いながら。
While thinking, "Ah, if I don't do it quickly, it'll end!"
で、あの、同じ部屋に私の息子がいたんですけれども、
And, um, my son was in the same room with me...
あ、息子さんまで！
Even your son!
息子に「コメントちょっと送ってみていいと思う？」って言って聞いたら、
I asked my son, "Do you think it's okay if I send a comment?"
「いんじゃー？」って言って。
And he said, "Should be fine."
いい息子さんだー！
What a good son!
それで、もう本当に震える手でコメント打って、
So, with hands literally trembling, I typed the comment,
もう、「あ、早くエンターキーを！」って。
thinking, "Ah, quickly, the Enter key!"
そんな緊張してくださったんですか！
You were that nervous for me?!
はい。それでもう、ドキドキしながら...
Yes. And so, while my heart was pounding...
あの、送らせていただいたら、
um, I sent the message,
Suaraさんね、あの、コメント気づいてくださって。
and Suara-san, you noticed the comment.
もう、とっても嬉しかったです！
I was just so happy!
こよりもですし、見てた助手くんたちもものすごく...
Not just me, but the Joshu-kuns watching were also...
もう嬉しくて。やっぱりあの、見ていただけるっていうのが、
so delighted. Having you watch us,
Suaraさんとか、あの、アクアプラスさんもそうですし、
Suara-san, and the people at Aquaplus too,
公式の皆様にご覧いただけると本当に嬉しく恐縮なことなので。
having the official team watch is truly an honor and a privilege.
もう幸せでございました。ありがとうございます！
I was so happy. Thank you so much!
もう、すごい楽しくて見入っちゃいました。本当に。
I was having so much fun watching you. Really.
いや、嬉しいです！
I'm so glad to hear that!
もう、すごい長時間、ね、されてるのがすごいなと思って。
I thought it was amazing how you stream for such long hours.
本当に。はい。
Really. Yes.
もうその、ね、その日の夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたり。
I even listened to your singing stream that same night.
すごい体力だなって思いながら。
I was thinking, "What incredible stamina!"
もう楽しんでいるのは、ね、うたわれるものが本当に素晴らしい作品だったから、
I was enjoying myself because "Utawarerumono" is such a wonderful series,
ですので、そのうたわれるものとずっと付き合っていらっしゃる...
so, for you, who has been involved with the series for so long...
Suaraさんですけれども、推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
Suara-san, do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか？
A favorite character?
推しキャラは、やっぱりちょっと、エルルゥっていうことにして...
My favorite character... I'll have to say it's Eluluu...
あ、あ、て、て、て、て、て、てことは！
W-W-W-Wait, which means!
しておかないとね、ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれない。
otherwise, I might get poked with a fork.
いや、いや、いや。あ、もしかして、あの...
No, no, no. Ah, could it be, you know...
仲が良いですよね。あの、ね、中の方の、
because you're close. You know, with the "person inside,"
柚木涼香さんと。とっても仲良くさせていただいてて。
Yuzuki Ryoka-san. We're very good friends.
本当に、あの、アニメの、あの、放送の時からですね、
Actually, since the time the anime was airing,
2006年からずっと仲良くさせていただいてるっていう...
we've been close friends since 2006...
20年！そうですね、20年。
20 years! That's right, 20 years.
すごい！はい、もうそれは、エルルゥ推しですね。
Incredible! Yes, so it's definitely Eluluu oshi then.
ということで、エルルゥ推しということで、お願いします！
So, please put me down as an Eluluu fan!
こよりはもう、あの、アルルゥが大好きなので、
And since I love Aruruu so much,
エルルゥ、アルルゥで、姉妹で！姉妹で！
with Eluluu and Aruruu, we're like sisters! Sisters!
嬉しいです！
I'm so happy!
ということで、もうもっともっとお話ししたいんですけれども、
So, I'd love to talk even more, but...
時間が来てしまいまして。
our time is up.
もう本当に、今日は一緒に歌っていただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for singing with me today!
ありがとうございました。こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、
Thank you. Koyori-san, your truly soft,
優しい、温かい声に、こう包まれながら、
gentle, and warm voice—while being enveloped by it,
私も一緒にね、歌えて本当に幸せでした。
I was really happy to be able to sing with you.
恐縮でございました！
I'm humbled!
ありがとうございます。また是非色々ご一緒させて...
Thank you. I'd love to have another chance...
いただく機会があれば嬉しいです。是非是非、よろしくお願いします！
to collaborate again. By all means, looking forward to it!
ありがとうございます。ということで、Suaraさんでした！
Thank you. So, that was Suara-san!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
こよりのリズムラボ
[Title: Koyori's Rhythm Lab]
9th リミックス
[Title: 9th Remix]
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
Eventually, a woman will become beautiful
だいスキ！
Love you!
ドットに媚びての人生
A life of flirting with dots
本当の自分に出ない
The real me won't come out
あのダンスがセクシー
That dance is sexy
可愛い女並んで
Cute girls lined up
輝きたい 愛されたい
I want to shine, I want to be loved
歴史へ放っとけおかない
History won't leave you alone
華やか人生いきたい
I want to live a glamorous life
あぁ 悲しい歌流れる
Ah, a sad song flows
町の中 あなた歩く
You walk through the town
涙声流れちゃう
A tearful voice flows
どうしてなんだろう
I wonder why
壁を破れて
Break the wall
誰も信じられなきゃ
If you can't believe anyone
泣きたいだけ泣けばいい
If you just want to cry, then cry
だからも一度恋して
So love once more
毒の中過ごして
Living in poison
だいスキ！
Love you!
こっち見て
Look over here
マジだいスキ！
I really love you!
だいスキ！
Love you!
愛♡スクリーム！
[Title: Ai♡Scream!]
作詞：aim
作曲：DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
[Song: Ai Scream!]
[Lyrics: aim]
[Composer: DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto]
教えてもっとあなたのこと
Tell me more about yourself
Tell me more more more
聞かせてもっとあなたの声
Let me hear your voice more
Let me hear more more more
こんなドキドキ もう抑えきれない
This heart pounding, I can't hold it back anymore
Oh! I need you!
友達は卒業
Graduating from being friends
運命の私
I am your destiny
見つけてほしいの
I want you to find me
One
勇気を出して
Summoning my courage
Two
見つめる作戦
The staring strategy
Three
ふと目が合えば
If our eyes happen to meet
Four
止められない
I can't stop
Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this affection
Melt Melty
とけちゃうよ
It's melting
ねぇ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey
気づいてマイダーリン
Notice me, my darling
届け
Reach out
大好き
I love you
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Okay!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
こよりちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
マヨネーズ！
Mayonnaise!
よりもあなた！
More than that, I like you!
AZKiちゃん！
AZKi-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
こしあん つぶあん
Smooth bean paste or chunky bean paste?
よりもあなた！
More than that, I like you!
ラミィちゃん！
Lamy-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
お酒よりも
More than alcohol...
あなた！
I like you!
みんなー！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き こよりん！
Of course we love you, Koyorin!
止められない
I can't stop
Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this affection
Melt Melty
とけちゃうよ
It's melting
ねぇ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey
気づいてマイダーリン
Notice me, my darling
届け
Reach out
大好き
I love you
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Okay!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
お願い見つけてマイダーリン
Please find me, my darling
My darling My darling
お願い気づいてマイダーリン
Please notice me, my darling
My darling My darling
One
勇気を出して
Summoning my courage
Two
近づく作戦
The closing-in strategy
Three
手と手が触れて
Our hands touching
Four
止められない
I can't stop
Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this affection
Melt Melty
とけちゃうよ
It's melting
ねぇ ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey, hey
気づいてマイダーリン
Notice me, my darling
それは
That is...
あなた
You!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Okay!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Okay!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
叫びましょ
Let's scream it out
Scream!
Ice cream!
Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026
[Title: Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026]
定位置！
Standard position!
はあああ！
Haaaa!
ガツーン！！
Clash!!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
カッキーン！！
Clang!!
ホームラン
Home run
えっ！？
What!?
カッキーン！！
Clang!!
RELAY
作詞：カトウチヒロ
作曲：Konami Amusement (佐藤直之)
[Song: RELAY]
[Lyrics: Kato Chihiro]
[Composer: Konami Amusement (Sato Naoyuki)]
もう何十回 もう何百回も
Already tens of times, already hundreds of times...
もう何十回も
Already dozens of times,
何百回も
hundreds of times,
澄む空見上げてた
I looked up at the clear sky.
たどり着いた場所が
The place I arrived at
運命のダイアモンド
is the diamond of fate.
何千回も
Thousands of times,
何万回も
tens of thousands of times,
涙流した君へ
to you who shed tears,
ねえ 諦められなかったことはあったけれど
Hey, there were things I couldn't give up on,
憧れは限界だったかな
but maybe my longing had reached its limit.
もういらない 嘘にただもがくなんて
I don't need it anymore, just struggling in lies...
もったいないでしょ
it's such a waste, right?
それぞれの物語
As our respective stories
交差する瞬間を
intersect for a moment,
見つめる秘密は...
the secret we gaze upon is...
放て夢だけ
Release only your dreams,
大きな声抱いて
holding a loud voice,
弾けそうな煌めきも 消えることなく
the sparkle about to burst will never fade.
どこまででも
To wherever it may be,
世界の向こうに
to the other side of the world,
届けてよ
deliver it!
終わることのない
This heartbeat in my chest
この胸の鼓動は
that will never end,
どうしても どうしても
no matter what, no matter what,
僕を呼んでいたから
because it was calling out to me.
その先へと 走り続ける
Beyond that, I'll keep on running,
次へ 次へと
to the next, and the next!
全国制覇おめでとう！
[On-screen: Congratulations on winning the nationals!]
妄想だっちゅうの
I say it's a delusion,
中途半端な
going down a halfway
深い坂下って
steep slope.
脱ぎ尽くしていたと
The realistic eyes that had cast
リアルな目はプレリュード
everything off are a prelude.
何千回も
Thousands of times,
何万回も
tens of thousands of times,
いいように続けて君へ
to you who kept going in a good way,
ねえ 聞かせてよ 夢はどんな音だって
hey, let me hear what sound your dream makes.
諦めが完敗ならば
If giving up is a total defeat,
絶対にないよ
it's definitely not happening.
誰に邪魔させようと
No matter who tries to interfere,
躊躇わないで
don't hesitate.
たくさんの情熱を
Connect many passions
落とさずに繋いでゆく
without ever dropping them,
そう 最後まで
yes, until the very end.
フラグに誓い
Swearing on the flag,
惜しく弾けて
bursting regretfully,
鳴り止まないファンファーレ
the fanfare that won't stop ringing,
いつの心に
into the distant future
流れていた
that was flowing
遠い未来へ
in my heart at some point,
祈るよ
I pray.
忘れられない
Following and following
あの日々の後悔を
the regrets of those days I can't forget,
追いかけて 追いかけて
this feeling that slid in
滑り込んだ この想い
overflowed into the blue sky,
青い空に ふと溢れてた
suddenly and far away,
遠く遠く
far, far away.
目覚めては繰り返す
Waking up and repeating the cycle,
眠い朝は
on sleepy mornings,
襟のタイを
tightening the tie
きつく締め
of my collar,
教室のドア
passing through
くぐると
the classroom door,
ほんの少し
I can walk
胸を張って
with a little
歩き出せる
bit of pride.
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
In such an everyday life, a breeze blows through.
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I sensed it.
震え出す 今この胸で
Right now, in this trembling chest,
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was already coming.
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
As billions of stars fade away,
見送った
I saw them off,
手を振った
waved goodbye,
よかったねと
and said 'I'm glad for you'.
手を振った
I waved my hand
よかったねと
Saying, "Good for you"
廊下の隅見下ろす 掃除の途中
I look down at the corner of the hallway in the middle of cleaning
おかしなものだと思う
I think it's a strange thing
あたしの中の時は止まってるのに
Even though the time inside of me has stopped
違う日々を生きてるように
It feels like I'm living through different days
誇りは雪のように降り積む
Dust falls and accumulates like snow
待ってる気がした
I realized you're waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I realized you're calling
震え出す今この時が
Now in this time that started to tremble
見つけた気がした
I realized I found it
失われた記憶が呼び覚ました
My lost memories recalled
物語
My story
永遠のその終わり
Of eternity, its ending
昨日は遠く明日はすぐ
Yesterday was far away, tomorrow was right ahead
そんな当たり前に心が踊った
That natural fact made my heart dance
聞こえた気がした
I realized I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I realized I felt it
震え出す今この胸で
Now in my chest that started to tremble
もう来る気がした
I realized it was coming already
幾千の朝を越え
A new sun overcame thousands of mornings
新しい日が
A new sun...
待ってる気がした
I realized you're waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I realized you're calling
震えてるこの魂が
My soul is trembling
見つけた気がした
I realized I found it
幾億の夢のように消え去れる日を
The day that's able to disappear like millions of dreams
見送った
I saw off
手を振った
I waved my hand
ありがとうと
Saying, "Thank you"
ぽつり灯り 管制塔
A faintly lit control tower
砂嵐の向こうへ
Toward the other side of the sandstorm
祈るように綴った
Written down like a prayer
これからのこと
Things to come
管制塔より
[Song: From the Control Tower]
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name anonymous requested
お便り 届いていますか
Has my message reached you?
この世界がいつからか
Since when did this world...
まるで他人事のように
...feel like someone else's business?
やけに静かなので
Because it is so terribly quiet
不安になったのです
I became anxious
思い出したのです
And I remembered
人知れず口を噤んだまま
While keeping my mouth shut without anyone knowing
終われないのです
I cannot let it end
それは嫌なのです
I hate that
夢って もっと わがままだったでしょう
Dreams were supposed to be more selfish, weren't they?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ
Answer me, laugh at me, notice me
此処に居るのにな、意地悪だな
Even though I am right here, you are being mean
誰にも届かない光を
This light that reaches no one...
どうしたら、伝えられるのでしょう
...how can I convey it?
どうしても、伝えたいよ
No matter what, I want to tell you
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
意気地無しなのでしょうか
Am I a coward?
それともこの世界には ぼくはお邪魔でしょうか
Or am I a nuisance to this world?
だとしても綴るよ
Even so, I will write it down
みっともなく叫ぶよ
I will shout unseemly
フラれたって好きだよ
Even if I get dumped, I love you
いいでしょ いいでしょ
That's fine, right? That's fine, right?
楽しかったよね
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は、嫌だ
I don't want to talk to myself anymore
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
「別に待ってないよ」
"I wasn't waiting at all"
夢と呼んだそれもぼくだっただけ
It was just me who called it a dream
もういいかい
Is it okay now?
応えてよ、
Answer me,
笑ってよ、
laugh for me,
気付いてよ
notice me
此処に居るのにな、
Even though I'm right here,
意地悪だな
you're so mean
誰にも届かない
Towards the light
光を
that reaches no one
ぼくだけは
I alone
光と呼び続ける
will continue to call it light
真夜中
In the middle of the night
管制塔から
from the control tower
あなたを明かしてやる
I will illuminate you
特報
[Special News]
新アニメーションMV 公開
[New Animated MV Release]
歌 博衣こより
[Vocals: Hakuiri Koyori]
作詞・作曲 堀江晶太
[Lyrics/Composition: Horie Shouta]
新アニメーションMV
[New Animated MV]
応えてよ、
Answer me,
笑ってよ、
laugh for me,
気付いてよ
notice me
此処に居るのにな、
Even though I'm right here,
意地悪だな
you're so mean
誰にも届かない
Towards the light
光を
that reaches no one
どうしたら、伝えられるのでしょう
How can I convey it to you?
どうしても、伝えたいよ
I want to convey it, no matter what
管制塔より
[From the Control Tower]
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
[Premiere Release Right After the Live]
ということで！
And so!
新曲のお披露目、フルアニメーションMV公開の告知、
The reveal of the new song, the announcement of the animated MV,
新3Dのお披露目、3個ドドンとまとめさせていただきました！
and the reveal of the new 3D model—I've presented all three!
イエーイ！
Yay!
情報量多かったけど、ついてきてるかな？
There was a lot of information, but are you keeping up?
はい、ちょっとね新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど、
Yes, I think you might be distracted because the new 3D is so cute,
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください。
but first, let me talk about the original song.
お披露目させていただいたのは、新曲『管制塔より』！
What I revealed was the new song, "Kanseitou yori"!
はい！ついにあの堀江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
Yes! It was finally written for me by Horie Shouta!
みんなどうだった？エモい？よかった？
How was it, everyone? Emotional? Good?
はい、そしてですね、今ちょっと映像も流してすごいって言ってくれててめっちゃ嬉しいんですけど、
Yes, and I'm so happy that you're saying the footage playing right now is amazing,
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
but right after this live ends, the full animated MV will have its premiere!
多分もう、マネちゃんがポチッとしてくれてると思います！
I think my manager has already clicked the button!
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわられている映像作品になっているので、
It's a visual work with a very carefully crafted worldview,
何回も見て聴いて、そしてちょっと世界観の考察とかしてみてください！
so please watch it many times, and try to speculate about its story!
そして、お待たせしました！
And then, thank you for waiting!
あ、ちょっと待って、1個言い忘れました。
Oh wait, I forgot one thing.
さっきの曲『管制塔より』、24時にリリースもあります！よろしくお願いします！
The song "Kanseitou yori" will also be released at midnight! Please check it out!
そしてですね、お待たせしました、新3D！
And then, here it is, the new 3D model!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛い？
How is it? Is it cute? Is it cute? Is it cute?
はい、もっとね余すことなく見せたいんだけど、イエーイ！
Yes, I want to show it to you in even more detail, yay!
ちょっと桃子ママの、あの、あれ、いつものにすごい近くなったんじゃないかなと思います！
I think it's become very close to Momoko-mama's original design!
この後のメン限ライブでね、撮影会もしまして、さらに細かく見せちゃうので、
In the members-only live after this, we'll have a photo session to show it off,
ぜひメン限ライブも来てください！
so please come to the members-only live too!
メン限ライブでは本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの、みんなが大好きな曲、
In the members-only live, I'll also sing that game song everyone loves,
キンキンキンも歌うよ！お楽しみに！
Kin Kin Kin! Look forward to it!
じゃあ1つだけ新3Dのめっちゃ変わったポイント教えちゃうと...
Now, I'll tell you just one major change in the new 3D...
ケモノ耳が揺れます！
The animal ears wiggle!
うわあ！可愛い！
Whoa! So cute!
ピー！
Pee!
はい！ということでね！
Alright! So with that...
あ、あとトレンド1位も本当にありがとうございます！
Oh, and thank you so much for being #1 on trending!
今日無理かなーって思ってたんで、めっちゃ嬉しかったし、
I thought it might be impossible today, so I'm so happy!
トレンド爆散！なんかすごいいっぱい入ってたみたいで！
Trending explosion! It seems there were so many entries!
本当にありがとー！
Thank you so much!
それでは！
Now then!
もう一つ大事なお知らせです！
I have another important announcement!
ドン！
Boom!
[博衣こよ誕生日記念2026]
[Hakui Koyori Birthday Celebration 2026]
博衣こより誕生日記念グッズ2026が発売されます！
Hakui Koyori's Birthday Celebration Goods 2026 are now on sale!
よー！
Yay!
早速詳細を見ていきましょう！
Let's take a look at the details right away!
まず一つ目はこちら！
First up is this!
もふこよにもなれる！？2Wayブランケット！
Can you become Mofukoyo?! 2-Way Blanket!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいるこよりの描き下ろしイラストです！
It features a newly drawn illustration of Koyori enjoying games in her room!
イラストはもちろん、ももこママ！
The illustration is, of course, by Momoko-mama!
これ丸めると、もふこよに早変わりして、
If you roll it up, it quickly turns into Mofukoyo,
持ち運びも楽ちんだし、そのままでも飾っても可愛いです！
making it easy to carry, and it's cute even if you just display it as is!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー 〜ゲーム実況編〜！
Voice Keychain ~Game Commentary Edition~!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！
The long-awaited voice keychain is here!
こよりの撮り下ろしボイスが入っているもので、
It includes newly recorded voices of Koyori,
今回はライブに合わせて、ゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、
and this time, to match the live, it has lines that sound like a game commentary,
絶叫が6種類入っております！
including 6 types of screams!
セリフはこよが考えました！
I came up with the lines myself!
イラストはなもり先生です！
The illustration is by Namori-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
Director Koyori Plushie Smartphone Stand!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよ！可愛い！
That Director Koyori is finally a plushie! So cute!
そのまま飾るもよし、スマホスタンドにもなるので、
You can display it as is, or use it as a smartphone stand,
超便利です！絶対ゲットしてね！
so it's super convenient! Be sure to get one!
最後はこちら！
Lastly, this one!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
Game Console-style Card Holder!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとか、ホロカも入れられて、
You can put in the bonus polaroid-style bromides or Holocards,
持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
and carry them with you in this card holder!
中に入っている台紙のイラストは、こよちゃんが描きました！
The illustration on the insert was drawn by me, Koyo-chan!
ゲーム機風のデザインもレトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない！？
Doesn't the game console design look retro and cute?!
はい！そして、フルセット特典はこちらです！
Yes! And here is the full set bonus!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドが付きます！
It comes with a polaroid-style bromide drawn by Momoko-mama!
数量限定版は直筆サインと箔押し、複製メッセージ入り、
The limited edition has a handwritten signature, foil stamping, and a printed message,
通常版は箔押しの複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！
while the regular edition has a foil-stamped signature and message!
販売開始がこのあと21時10分にしてあるので！
Sales start later at 21:10!
皆さんあの、慌てないで大丈夫です！10分からなので！
Everyone, don't worry! It's from 10 past!
はい、あの、見てって下さい。よろしくお願いします！
Yes, please take a look. Thank you!
さらに特典ASMRボイスも付きます！
Plus, there's a bonus ASMR voice!
毎年恒例の、君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃうASMRボイス2026版！
The annual ASMR voice where I celebrate your birthday instead, 2026 version!
こちらですね、毎年みんな誕生日まで我慢して聴いて、
Everyone holds off listening until their birthday every year,
わーい！ってなってるの、すごく嬉しく思ってます。是非ゲットして下さい！
and it makes me so happy when they say 'Yay!'. Please do get it!
はい！ということで、怒涛のお知らせでした！
Alright! So that was a whirlwind of announcements!
可愛いでしょー！？みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて、
Isn't it cute?! Everyone's saying it's cute,
こよ嬉しいよー！表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ！
and I'm so happy! My expressions have changed a bit too!
にひゃー！これができるようになったりとか！
Nihya! I can do things like this now!
あとはキリッ！イエーイ！こんな表情もできるようになりました！
And also 'Sharp!' Yay! I can make expressions like this now!
面々をお楽しみに！ということで今日は、
Look forward to seeing everyone! So, for today,
博衣こより生誕ライブ2026、ゲームソングライブに見に来てくれて、
for coming to Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2026, the Game Song Live,
ありがとー！
thank you!
このあとですね、新曲のアニメMV公開と、
After this, the animated MV for my new song will be released,
メン限ライブ、ですね！アニメMV公開見て、
and then the members-only live! Watch the animated MV release,
で10分かな、グッズ買って、15分からメン限ライブって感じで、
then buy goods around 10 past, and the members-only live starts at 15 past,
ゆっくり順番に行けるようになっているので！
so you can go through everything step by step!
慌てず、駆けず、何だ、押さず！でよろしくお願いします！
Don't panic, don't run, and... don't push! Thank you!
ということで今日は、ちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど、
So for today, though I was a bit late,
この新3Dお披露目生誕ライブもできて、大好きなゲームソングいっぱいお披露目できて、
I was able to do this new 3D reveal birthday live and perform many of my favorite game songs,
嬉しかったよー！みんな本当に見に来てくれてありがとー！
and I'm so happy! Thank you all so much for coming to watch!
また会おうね！ありがとー！
Let's meet again! Thank you!
MV見てねー！
Watch the MV, okay?!